In this exercise, you'll be asked to create an SLA that
在此练习中 将要求您创建 SLA
represents the up time and downtime of your platform.
表示平台的启动时间和停机时间
I've laid out a couple of steps that probably need to be included in your SLA.
我已经列出了可能需要包含在 SLA中的几个步骤
Section 1 would include your own applications,
第 1 节将包含您自己的应用程序
that things that your company creates and are critical for your customers.
你的公司创造的东西对你的顾客至关重要
What would be included there and what the SLA would be for those components.
将包括哪些内容以及 SLA 将用于这些组件的内容
The second part of the SLA would cover things like third-parties,
SLA 的第二部分将涵盖第三方
and what third party SLAs look like
还有哪些第三方 SLA
or how that comes into play in your relationship with your customers.
或者在你与客户的关系中如何发挥作用
Finally, I would have a section that covered non-critical components.
最后 我将有一节讨论非关键部分
Things that are useful or nice to have,
那些有用或善良的东西
but not necessarily critical to the application and
但不一定对应用至关重要
how those would be included or considered by your customers.
您的客户将如何包括或考虑这些内容
Together, all three of these make up a good picture of what
这三者共同组成了一个好的画面
is or is not covered by your SLA. Good luck.
是或不属于您的 SLA  祝你好运